[
  {
    "question": "Which running back holds the record for the most yards in an NFL game?",
    "choice1": "Adrian Peterson",
    "choice2": "Walter Payton",
    "choice3": "Eric Dickerson",
    "choice4": "Barry Sanders",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NFL Quarterback came back from a 28-3 lead to win Super Bowl 51?",
    "choice1": "Tom Brady",
    "choice2": "Joe Montana",
    "choice3": "Shaquille O'Neal",
    "choice4": "Tony Romo",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player was the youngest player to ever win the MVP award?",
    "choice1": "Lebron James",
    "choice2": "Derrick Rose",
    "choice3": "Kobe Bryant",
    "choice4": "Tim Duncan",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NFL Quarterback that was recently drafted went to Allen High School in Allen, TX?",
    "choice1": "Marcus Mariota",
    "choice2": "Baker Mayfield",
    "choice3": "Kyler Murray",
    "choice4": "Lamar Jackson",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NFL team has the most Super Bowl wins?",
    "choice1": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "choice2": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "choice3": "San Francisco 49ers",
    "choice4": "Minnesota Vikings",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NFL team lost four consecutive Super Bowls in a row and has never won a Super Bowl?",
    "choice1": "Minnesota Vikings",
    "choice2": "Cleveland Browns",
    "choice3": "Detroit Lions",
    "choice4": "Buffalo Bills",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Boxers has never lost a professional fight?",
    "choice1": "Floyd Mayweather",
    "choice2": "Muhammad Ali",
    "choice3": "Mike Tyson",
    "choice4": "Conor Mcgregor",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following NBA players was drafted straight out of High School?",
    "choice1": "Michael Jordan",
    "choice2": "Scottie Pippen",
    "choice3": "Kevin Garnett",
    "choice4": "Stephen Curry",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NFL Quarterback has won the most MVP awards?",
    "choice1": "Tom Brady",
    "choice2": "Peyton Manning",
    "choice3": "Aaron Rodgers",
    "choice4": "Drew Brees",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points did Kobe Bryant score in his final NBA game?",
    "choice1": "40",
    "choice2": "50",
    "choice3": "60",
    "choice4": "70",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
